# **DILPREET TUNG**

219 Red sky crescent NE, Calgary, AB, T3N 1R2 204-590-9762 diltung88@yahoo.ca

Skilled customer service specialist with proven ability to perform variety of tasks, including maintenance, billing, cash management and special projects. Energetic, driven, and reliable with proven ability to reach and exceed company and personal goals. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success by establishing rapport with clients.

#### **SKILLS**

- Merchandising and stocking
- Retail experience
- POS System
- Cash Drawer Management
- Refunds and exchanges
- Skilled in conflict resolution
- Social skills
- Makeup and skincare
- Product knowledge
- Fluent in Hindi and Punjabi

#### **EDUCATION**

U1 student 2018-2021

University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, MB

Sisler high school 2014-2018

# WORK HISTORY

# **Shoppers Beauty Specialist**

Sept 2020- Aug 2021

- Greeting all incoming and outgoing guests, whether in boutique or other parts of the store.
- Showed customers how to apply makeup and other products to achieve desired looks.
- Recommended appropriate products to meet customer's individual needs and specific concerns.
- Capitalized on upselling opportunities for additional products and services to increase sales numbers.
- Backed up reception desk by answering phones, scheduling appointments and processing payments.
- Displayed merchandise to present visually appealing arrangements that drive sales.
- Restocked shelves, pulled items forward and helped customers locate items.

## Think kitchen key holder

Jan 2021- July 2021

- Opening and closing the store, cash drawer management.
- Processing payments, returns and exchanges.
- Acknowledge customers, help locate product and provide information.
- Receiving, unpacking, and placing the products in the appropriate places.
- Storing extra merchandise on backroom shelves.
- Placing postings according to current promotions and as directed by head officT3e.
- Informing customers about store promotions and meeting sales goals.

McDonald's June 2018- Nov 2020

- Working at the front counter helping customers through the ordering process, maintaining a fast speed of service, ensuring items are well stocked, assembling orders and processing payments.

#### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

## Ford DRIVE4UR community

(May 12, 2017-3 hours)

Greeting people and explaining the sign-up procedure for a test drive.

WE charity 2017

Raising funds for countries who are enduring pressing issues like hunger, poverty and access to education.

## **REFERENCES**

#### **Marina Hofer**

Beauty manager Shopper's Drug mart, Winnipeg, MB (204) 997-8790

#### Raman Khangura

Assistant manager Think Kitchen, Winnipeg, MB (431) 335-4948 Ramankhangura\_14@yahoo.com

## **Kunal Aggarwal**

Manager McDonald's, Winnipeg, MB (204) 590-9297. Aggkunal@live.com